Archibald M. Crossley Papers 1999.0007
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Consumer Studies, undated, 1927-1969
  - Subseries C: Various, undated, 1928-1969
    - J. Walter Thompson Co.
      - Beer and Ale Sales and Distribution Study: New York, NY, [1937] December (Box 17:, Folder 1016)
      - Beer Consumption Study, 1944 April (Box 17:, Folder 1017)
      - Beer Consumption Survey, 1949 June (Box 17:, Folder 1018)
      - Beer and Ale Preferences and Habits Study, 1951 June (Box 17:, Folder 1019)
      - Beer and Ale Consumption Survey (with supplemental tabulations), 1954 May-June (Box 17:, Folder 1020)
    - [ King Features]--Syndicate Pattern Study (tabulations only), 1949 August (Box 17:, Folder 1021)
    - Kirsten Pipes--Kirsten Pipe Dealer Survey (tabulations only), 1940 March (Box 17:, Folder 1022)
    - Kirsten Pipes--Kirsten Pipe Dealer Survey: New York, NY (tabulations only), 1940 March (Box 17:, Folder 1023)
    - Koppers Co., Inc.--Koppers Coke Survey: Brooklyn, NY (tabulations only), 1938 March (Box 17:, Folder 1024)
    - Lehn and Fink, Inc.--Lysol National Market Report, 1939 September (Box 17:, Folder 1025)
    - Lehn and Fink, Inc.--Commercial Use of Disinfectants Survey, 1940 March - April (Box 17:, Folder 1026)
    - Lehn and Fink, Inc.--Lysol Cross-Section Survey, 1940 April (Box 17:, Folder 1027)
    - Lennen and Mitchell, Inc.
      - Unidentified Toilet Soap Use Study (tabulations only), undated (Box 17:, Folder 1028)
      - Unidentified Tooth Powder and Paste Survey (tabulations only), [1940 February] (Box 17:, Folder 1029)
      - General Electric Radio Set Ownership Study (Background and Field Materials), 1943 (Box 17:, Folder 1030)
      - General Electric Radio Set Ownership Study (tabulations), 1943 (Box 17:, Folder 1031)
      - General Electric Radio Set Ownership Study (tabulations continued), 1943 (Box 17:, Folder 1032)
      - Railroad Equipment Advertising Survey (tabulationsonly), 1945 November (Box 17:, Folder 1033)
      - Whiskey Brand Consumer Demand Survey (tabulations only), 1946 March (Box 17:, Folder 1034)
    - Lunt Silversmiths--Sterling Silverware Pattern Study (tabulations only), 1948 September (Box 17:, Folder 1035)
    - Lyn Baker Advertising--Cat Food Study (with supplemental tabulations), 1951 October (Box 17:, Folder 1036)
    - Marlboro Toy Co.--Probable Market for Childrens' Automobiles Study (tabulations only), 1948 March (Box 18:, Folder 1037)
    - McCann Erickson, Inc.
      - Quick Advertisements Visibility Study Notes, undated (Box 18:, Folder 1038)
      - Pork Sausage Consumer Survey: Detroit, MI (tabulations only), 1940 February (Box 18:, Folder 1039)
      - Pork Sausage Dealer Survey: Detroit, MI (tabulations only), 1940 February (Box 18:, Folder 1040)
      - Peoria Rub Survey, 1940 March (Box 18:, Folder 1041)
      - Correspondences Re: Stromberg-Carlson Radio Survey, 1944 April - October (Box 18:, Folder 1042)
    - Melnor Industries--Research Proposal, undated (Box 18:, Folder 1043)
    - Miss Fine's School--Trustee Report, 1949 March (Box 18:, Folder 1044)
    - National Association of Broadcasters--San Antonio Shopping Habits Among Women, 1946 April (Box 18:, Folder 1045)
    - National Cash Register Co.--Effect of Business Conditions on Business Equipment Market Survey, [1938] (Box 18:, Folder 1046)
    - National Research Organization--Brand Competition Report (Dentifrice Market), 1933 (Box 18:, Folder 1047)
    - National Research Organization--Brand Competition Report (Tea Market), 1933 (Box 18:, Folder 1048)
    - National Standard Parts Association--Automobile Parts Pilot Study, 1948 March - April (Box 18:, Folder 1049)
    - [Office of Production Management, Salvage Division]
      - Product Consumption Study, Background Information, 1942 June (Box 18:, Folder 1050)
      - Product Consumption Study, Special Tabulations On the Index, undated (Box 18:, Folder 1051)
      - Product Consumption Study, Special Tabulations On the Index (Magazine Coverage), undated (Box 18:, Folder 1052)
      - Product Consumption Study, Surveys and Tabulations Forms, undated (Box 18:, Folder 1053)
      - Product Consumption Study, Commodities of Consumption By Cities: Syracuse, NY, 1942 April - 1943 March (Box 18:, Folder 1054)
      - Product Consumption Study, Commodities of Consumption By Cities: Grand Rapids, MI, 1942 June - 1943 March (Box 18:, Folder 1055)
      - Product Consumption Study, Commodities of Consumption By Cities: Louisville, KY, 1942 June - 1943 March (Box 18:, Folder 1056)
      - Product Consumption Study, Three-City Totals By Income:, 1942 June - September (Box 18:, Folder 1057)
      - Product Consumption Study, Commodities of Consumption By Cities: Pittsburgh, PA, 1942 July - 1943 March (Box 18:, Folder 1058)
      - Product Consumption Study, Commodities of Consumption By Cities: Dallas, TX, 1942 August - 1943 March (Box 18:, Folder 1059)
      - Product Consumption Study, Commodities of Consumption By Cities: Portland, OR, 1942 August - 1943 March (Box 18:, Folder 1060)
      - Product Consumption Study, Commodities of Consumption By Cities: Omaha, NE, 1942 September - 1943 March (Box 18:, Folder 1061)
      - Product Consumption Study, Six-City Totals By Income, 1942 September - October (Box 18:, Folder 1062)
      - Product Consumption Study, Prelimenary Bathroom Inventory Tests, 1942 October - December (Box 18:, Folder 1063)
      - Product Consumption Study, Prelimenary Kitchen Inventory Tests, 1942 November - December (Box 18:, Folder 1064)
      - Product Consumption Study, Ten-City Totals By Income, 1942 November - 1942 April (Box 18:, Folder 1065)
      - Product Consumption Study, Commodities of Consumption By Cities: Birmingham, AL, 1943 January - March (Box 18:, Folder 1066)
      - Product Consumption Study, Commodities of Consumption By Cities: Providence, RI, 1943 January - March (Box 18:, Folder 1067)
      - Product Consumption Study, Commodities of Consumption By Cities: St. Louis, MO, 1943 January - March (Box 18:, Folder 1068)
    - Pacific Mills--Report on Pacific Mills Survey (tabulations only), 1940 January (Box 18:, Folder 1069)
    - Parker--National Fountain Pen and Ink Buying Habits, undated (Box 18:, Folder 1070)
    - Parker--Fountain Pen Preference Study: Chicago, IL (tabulations only), 1941 December (Box 18:, Folder 1071)
    - Pepsi-Cola Co.--Influence of Scholarship Program on Younger Soft Drink Users Study, 1948 August (Box 18:, Folder 1072)
    - [ Process Development Corp.]--National Dentifrice and Mouthwash Market Study (tabulations only), [1948 September] (Box 18:, Folder 1073)
    - Procter and Gamble Co.--Methods of Brushing Teeth Study, 1943 [April] (Box 18:, Folder 1074)
    - [ R.B. Davis]--Chocolate Beverage Survey: Harrisburg, PA, 1941 January (Box 19:, Folder 1075)
    - Reach, Yates, and Mattoon, Inc.--Chicago Recall Telephone Study, 1954 February (Box 19:, Folder 1076)
    - Reader Mail, Inc.--Cincinnati Dressmaker Opinion Study, 1945 June (Box 19:, Folder 1077)
    - Reed and Barton Silversmiths--Plated Silverware Patter Study, 1948 June (Box 19:, Folder 1078)
    - Reed and Barton Silversmiths--Sterling Silverware Pattern Study, 1948 August (Box 19:, Folder 1079)
    - Reiss Advertising--E-Z-Do Closets and Chests Study, 1947 March (Box 19:, Folder 1080)
    - R.J. Reynolds Co.--Sales Analysis of Cigarette Brands (tabulation agenda, no data), 1938 July (Box 19:, Folder 1081)
    - Schlitz Brewing Co.--Beer Markets in the United States Study, 1946 December (Box 19:, Folder 1082)
    - [ Snowdrift Co., Inc.]--Unidentified Shortening Study, undated (Box 19:, Folder 1083)
    - [ Snowdrift Co., Inc.]--Wesson Oil Southern Market Study, 1939 (Box 19:, Folder 1084)
    - Spool Cotton Company--Spool Cotton Consumer Survey, [1935] (Box 19:, Folder 1085)
    - Standard Brands, Inc.
      - Yeast Survey, 1945 August - October (Box 19:, Folder 1086)
      - Pudding Survey, 1948 August (Box 19:, Folder 1087)
      - Coffee Usage Survey, 1948 September (Box 19:, Folder 1088)
      - Instant Tea Consumer Reaction Study: Albany, NY, 1948 September (Box 19:, Folder 1089)
      - Instant Tea Survey: Binghampton, NY, 1948 November (Box 19:, Folder 1090)
      - Comparative Use of Instant and Regular Coffee Survey, 1949 May (Box 19:, Folder 1091)
    - [ Standard Oil Company of New York]--Public Attitudes Toward SOCONY Oil Burners Study (tabulations only), undated (Box 19:, Folder 1092)
    - State Farm Mutual Auto Insurance Co.--Automobile Insurance Study Proposal, 1962 December (Box 19:, Folder 1093)
    - Sterling Silversmiths Guild of America--Sterling Silver National Survey, [1928] (Box 19:, Folder 1094)
    - Sterling Silversmiths Guild of America--Post-War Sterling Silver Market Development Research Plan, 1945 May (Box 19:, Folder 1095)
    - Textron, Inc.--Design Testing Memorandum, 1949 April (Box 19:, Folder 1096)
    - Time, Inc.--Commercial Vehicle Operation Study: Kalamazoo, MI, 1949 April (Box 19:, Folder 1097)
    - Unidentified Sponsors
      - Automotive Tire Consumer Study Proposal, undated (Box 19:, Folder 1098)
      - Beer Advertising Study, undated (Box 19:, Folder 1099)
      - Beer and Ale Survey (Bar Check), undated (Box 19:, Folder 1100)
      - Beer and Ale Survey (Bar Patrons), undated (Box 19:, Folder 1101)
      - Beer and Ale Survey (Street Interviews), undated (Box 19:, Folder 1102)
      - Beer Consumption Study, undated (Box 19:, Folder 1103)
      - [Consolidated Catalogue Study], undated (Box 19:, Folder 1104)
      - Crossley Retail Reports: Buying Habits of Consumers Studies, undated (Box 19:, Folder 1105)
      - Ford and Chevrolet Buyer Mail Survey (tabulations only), undated (Box 19:, Folder 1106)
      - Gasoline and Oil Brands Advertising Study (tabulations only), undated (Box 19:, Folder 1107)
      - Industrial Employee Uniforming Survey (tabulations only), undated (Box 19:, Folder 1108)
      - Random Automotive Survey (tabulations only), undated, 1950 (Box 19:, Folder 1109)
      - Shredded Wheat Study, undated (Box 19:, Folder 1110)
      - Truck Fleet Survey (tabulations only), undated (Box 19:, Folder 1111)
      - Unidentified American Druggist and Drug Topics Study (tabulations only), undated (Box 20:, Folder 1112)
      - Unidentified Antifreeze Study, undated (Box 20:, Folder 1113)
      - Unidentified Automotive Survey, undated (Box 20:, Folder 1114)
      - Unidentified Beer Study, undated (Box 20:, Folder 1115)
      - Unidentified Cold Tablet Study, undated (Box 20:, Folder 1116)
      - Unidentified Silverware Study: Philadelphia, PA, undated (Box 20:, Folder 1117)
      - Unidentified Soft Drink Study, undated (Box 20:, Folder 1118)
      - Pequot Sheet Survey, 1935 January (Box 20:, Folder 1119)
      - Household Bar Soap Study (tabulations only), 1936 August - 1937 January (Box 20:, Folder 1120)
      - Toilet Soap Study (tabulations only), 1936 August - 1937 January (Box 20:, Folder 1121)
      - Anchor Line Bed Sheet Study: Washington, DC, 1937 April (Box 20:, Folder 1122)
      - Laundry Starch Product Test, 1938 February (Box 20:, Folder 1123)
      - All-Purpose Liquid Cleanser Opinon Survey, 1938 August (Box 20:, Folder 1124)
      - Consumer Attitude Re:Sterling Silver Market Problems Study, 1939 April (Box 20:, Folder 1125)
      - Corset Survey: Chicago, IL (tabulations only), 1939 November (Box 20:, Folder 1126)
      - Typewriter Survey, [1940 February] (Box 20:, Folder 1127)
      - Automotive Dealers Survey (tabulations only), 1940 July (Box 20:, Folder 1128)
      - Manufacturer's Viewpoint on Department Stores Study (tabulations only), [1940 July] (Box 20:, Folder 1129)
      - Massachusetts Alcoholic Beverage Survey, 1940 July 25 (Box 20:, Folder 1130)
      - Massachusetts Alcoholic Beverage Survey, 1940 July 31 (Box 20:, Folder 1131)
      - New Car Owner Automotive Survey (tabulations only), 1940 July (Box 20:, Folder 1132)
      - Razor and Razor Blades Survey Report, 1940 July (Box 20:, Folder 1133)
      - Baking Powder Study (tabulations only), 1940 August (Box 20:, Folder 1134)
      - Report On Beer Association Test, 1941 July (Box 20:, Folder 1135)
      - Report On Beer Association Test: New York, NY, 1941 September (Box 20:, Folder 1136)
      - Baking Powder Study (tabulations only), 1941 October (Box 20:, Folder 1137)
      - Report On Beer Association Test: New York, NY, 1941 December (Box 20:, Folder 1138)
      - Buses and Small Truck/Commercial Cars Ownership Study (tabulations only), [1943 August] (Box 20:, Folder 1139)
      - Buses and Small Truck/Commercial Cars Ownership Study (reference material), undated (Box 20:, Folder 1140)
      - Use of Trucks and Commerical Cars Study, 1943 August (Box 20:, Folder 1141)
      - Oil and Rubber Industry Consumer Study, 1943 September (Box 20:, Folder 1142)
      - Report on Prelimenary Technique Test: Cigarette Attitude Study, 1944 February (Box 20:, Folder 1143)
      - Beer Consumption Study (tabulations only), 1944 April (Box 20:, Folder 1144)
      - Packaged Beer Preferences Survey, 1944 December (Box 20:, Folder 1145)
      - Silverware Study: Atlanta, GA, 1945 September (Box 20:, Folder 1146)
      - Silverware Study: Dallas, TX, 1945 September (Box 20:, Folder 1147)
      - Silverware Study: Milwaukee, WI, 1945 September (Box 20:, Folder 1148)
      - Silverware Study: Pittsburgh, PA, 1945 September (Box 20:, Folder 1149)
      - Silverware Study: Indianapolis, IN, 1946 January (Box 20:, Folder 1150)
      - Unidentified Beer Study, 1947 February (Box 20:, Folder 1151)
      - Gift Reception Survey, [1948 January] (Box 20:, Folder 1152)
      - Unidentified Truck Survey, 1949 (Box 20:, Folder 1153)
      - Toiletry Purchase Pilot Study: Boonton, NJ (tabulations only), 1950 January (Box 20:, Folder 1154)
      - Tru-Tint Advertising Study Plan, 1952 February (Box 20:, Folder 1155)
      - Tru-Tint Consumer Study (no tabulations), 1952 March (Box 20:, Folder 1156)
      - Unidentified Quilted Garments Study (no tabulations), 1954 February (Box 20:, Folder 1157)
      - Unidentified Weight Loss Study Press Release, 1955 August (Box 20:, Folder 1158)
    - United States Brewers' Foundation--Research Study Proposal, 1948 April (Box 20:, Folder 1159)
    - United States Chamber of Commerce, Business Division--Consumption Survey: Rochester, NY, [1929] (Box 20:, Folder 1160)
    - [ Vicks Chemical Co.]--Vick Product Shopping Check Study (Division No. 101), 1937 March (Box 20:, Folder 1161)
    - [ Vicks Chemical Co.]--Vick Product Shopping Check Study (Division No. 102), 1937 March (Box 20:, Folder 1162)
    - [ Vicks Chemical Co.]--Vicks Shopping Check Study (Division No. 105, tabulations only), 1937 March (Box 20:, Folder 1163)
    - [ Vick's Chemical Co.]--Vicks Shopping Check Study (Division No. 106, tabulations only), 1937 March (Box 20:, Folder 1164)
    - W.T. Grant Co.--Shopper Store Selection Study: Syracuse, NY, 1947 January (Box 20:, Folder 1165)
    - W.T. Grant Co.--Shopping Habits Survey, 1948 September (Box 20:, Folder 1166)
- Series II: Political Surveys, undated, 1936-1969
  - Subseries A: Crossley Inc., undated, 1936-1967
    - Albert Frank Guether Law, Inc., Advertising Agents: Wisconsin--State Public Opinion Study, 1947 November (Box 21:, Folder 1167)
    - Post Publishing Co.--Four county political attitudes study, 1953 December (Box 21:, Folder 1168)
    - Conservative and unionist central office--Correspondence re: Bandwagon effects of polls, 1967 January - February (Box 21:, Folder 1169)
    - Competitive Polling: Presidential election, 1964 (Box 21:, Folder 1170)
    - Competitive Polling: Methodology and sampling, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1171)
    - Competitive Polling: Elmo Roper and Associates: Presidential election, 1960 November (Box 21:, Folder 1172)
    - Competitive Polling: Elmo Roper and Associates: "Were the Polls Wrong,", 1966 December (Box 21:, Folder 1173)
    - Competitive Polling: Gallup Organization, Inc.: Articles, 1945 January - 1967 January (Box 21:, Folder 1174)
    - Competitive Polling: Gallup Organization, Inc.: Presidential election, 1960 (Box 21:, Folder 1175)
    - Competitive Polling: Gallup Organization, Inc.: Look at the election polls report, 1964 September (Box 21:, Folder 1176)
    - Competitive Polling: Gallup Organization, Inc.: Pre-presidential election voter turnout study, [1968] (Box 21:, Folder 1177)
    - Competitive Polling: Public Opinion Survey, Inc.: New York State Congressional elctions study, 1962 March (Box 21:, Folder 1178-1179)
    - Competitive Polling: Public Opinion Survey, Inc.: Virginia State survey, 1962 November (Box 21:, Folder 1180)
    - Presidential election polls: articles, 1936 (Box 21:, Folder 1181)
    - Presidential election polls: press releases, 1936 (Box 21:, Folder 1182)
    - Presidential election polls: sampling, 1936 (Box 21:, Folder 1183)
    - Presidential election polls: articles, 1940 (Box 21:, Folder 1184)
    - Presidential election polls: Field materials, 1940 (Box 21:, Folder 1185)
    - Presidential election polls: New York, NY test poll, 1940 July - August (Box 21:, Folder 1186)
    - Presidential election polls: Press releases, 1940 (Box 21:, Folder 1187)
    - Presidential election polls: Promotional materials, 1940 (Box 21:, Folder 1188)
    - Presidential election polls: Public opnion and campaign strategy report, 1940 July (Box 21:, Folder 1189)
    - Presidential election polls: Various state polling figures, 1940 (Box 21:, Folder 1190)
    - Presidential election polls: articles, 1944 (Box 21:, Folder 1191)
    - Presidential election polls: Pre-election speech notes, 1944 (Box 21:, Folder 1192)
    - Presidential election polls: Correspondence, 1943 December - 1945 June (Box 21:, Folder 1193)
    - Presidential election polls: Field materials, 1944 (Box 21:, Folder 1194)
    - Presidential election polls: North Dakota state public opinion sample survey, 1944 September (Box 21:, Folder 1195)
    - Presidential election polls: Poll subscribers, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1196)
    - Presidential election polls: Post election analysis, 1944 (Box 21:, Folder 1197)
    - Presidential election polls: Press releases, 1944 (Box 21:, Folder 1198)
    - Presidential election polls: Promotional materials, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1199)
    - Presidential election polls: Sampling, 1944 (Box 21:, Folder 1200)
    - Presidential election polls: Synthesis of 1936-1944 presidential elections (Box 21:, Folder 1201)
    - Presidential election polls: Tabulation and anaylsis, 1944 (Box 21:, Folder 1202)
    - Presidential election polls: Archibald Crossley, 1948 (Box 21:, Folder 1203)
    - Presidential election polls: Committee on measurement of aopinion and attitudes and consumer wants correspondence, 1948 January - 1949 October (Box 21:, Folder 1204)
    - Presidential election polls: Correspondence, 1948 June - November (Box 21:, Folder 1205)
    - Presidential election polls: Elmira, NY, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1206)
    - Presidential election polls: Field materials, 1948 (Box 21:, Folder 1207)
    - Presidential election polls: Methodology, 1948 (Box 21:, Folder 1208)
    - Presidential election polls: Post-mortem corespondence, 1948 November - 1949 November (Box 21:, Folder 1209)
    - Presidential election polls: Post-mortem Iowa conference on attitude and opinion research, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1210)
    - Presidential election polls: Post-mortem Presidential vote study, 1949 April (Box 21:, Folder 1211)
    - Presidential election polls: Post-mortem press releases, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1212)
    - Presidential election polls: Post-mortem press releases--Crossley polls, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1213)
    - Presidential election polls: Post-mortem reactions, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1214)
    - Presidential election polls: Post-mortem reactions by Archibald M.Crossley, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1215)
    - Presidential election polls: Post-mortem Social Science Research Council (SSRC) Pre-election polls and forecasts study, 1948 December (Box 21:, Folder 1216)
    - Presidential election polls: Post-mortem Social Science Research Council (SSRC) Pre-election polls and forecasts study, Crossley contributions, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1217)
    - Presidential election polls: Post-mortem Social Science Research Council (SSRC) Pre-election polls and forecasts study correspondence, 1948 November - 1949 December (Box 21:, Folder 1218)
    - Presidential election polls: Post-mortem Social Science Research Council (SSRC) Pre-election polls and forecasts study, questions of interest and some findings, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1219)
    - Presidential election polls: Predictions by others, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1220)
    - Presidential election polls: Press releases, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1221)
    - Presidential election polls: Press releases (Crossley Polls), undated (Box 22:, Folder 1222)
    - Presidential election polls: Press releases (Gallup Polls), undated (Box 22:, Folder 1223)
    - Presidential election polls: Press releases (Roper Polls), undated (Box 22:, Folder 1224)
    - Presidential election polls: Press releases (Straw polls), undated (Box 22:, Folder 1225)
    - Presidential election polls: Promotional materials, undated (Box 22:, Folder 1226)
    - Presidential election polls: Tabulation and analysis, undated (Box 22:, Folder 1227)
    - Presidential election polls: Archibald M. Crossley articles, 1952 (Box 22:, Folder 1228)
    - Presidential election polls: Correspondence, 1952 January - November (Box 22:, Folder 1229)
    - Presidential election polls: Field materials, 1952 (Box 22:, Folder 1230)
    - Presidential election polls: Post-mortem press releases, 1952 (Box 22:, Folder 1231)
    - Presidential election polls: Press releases, 1952 (Box 22:, Folder 1232)
    - Presidential election polls: Press releases (Crossley Polls), 1952 (Box 22:, Folder 1233)
    - Presidential election polls: Promotional materials, 1952 (Box 22:, Folder 1234)
    - Presidential election polls: Subscribers, 1952 (Box 22:, Folder 1235)
    - Presidential election polls: Three county presidential preference poll Collier's Magazine, 1952 (Box 22:, Folder 1236)
    - Presidential election polls: Draft questionnaire for Study, 1954 August (Box 22:, Folder 1237)
    - Freedom and Union, Journal of the World Republic: Correspondence, 1949 September - October (Box 22:, Folder 1238)
    - Higginbotham, Hickenlooper, Foffenberger and Van Schmus: Cooperative modern sampling methods poll, undated (Box 22:, Folder 1239)
    - Hill, Blackett and Company advertising: Wisconsin State test of public opinion poll, 1947 June (Box 22:, Folder 1240)
    - The Psychological Corp.: New York State gubernatorial poll, 1946 August (Box 22:, Folder 1241)
    - Reuben H. Donnelly Corp.: Presidential election presentation, 1944 June (Box 22:, Folder 1242)
    - Reuben H. Donnelly Corp.: Pennsylvania State Campaign issues survey, 1944 July (Box 22:, Folder 1243)
    - Roper Public Opinion Research Center: Correspondence, 1961 September (Box 22:, Folder 1244)
    - Unidentified: National eligible voter population study, undated (Box 22:, Folder 1245)
    - Unidentified: Problems confronting the new administration study, undated (Box 22:, Folder 1246)
    - Unidentified study: Field material, undated (Box 22:, Folder 1247)
    - Unidentified: Philadelphia city elections pilot poll, 1943 July (Box 22:, Folder 1248)
    - Unidentified: New York State election sample design, [1946] (Box 22:, Folder 1249)
    - Unidentified: Wisconsin State presidential attitudes study, 1952 January (Box 22:, Folder 1250)
    - Unidentified: New Hampshire State voting preferences study, 1952 February (Box 22:, Folder 1251)
    - Unidentified: Pennsylvania State presidential attitutdes study, 1952 February (Box 22:, Folder 1252)